Hyung Jin Chung

Frontend developer

Email : devdaniel0426@gmail.com

Mobile : 021 0261 5453 Portfolio : devdaniels.com

Github : github.com/daniel0426 Linkedin : in/devdaniel-chung

I am a creative frontend developer who is highly adaptable and has experience in building, designing and maintaining websites and applications.

"Touch the world with technology" is the most appropriate phrase for why I got into this industry. Resolving inconveniences in common life and thinking & turning thoughts into reality is the most attractive and satisfying part of this industry.

Experience

Web developer & digital marketer (part-time)

Hipeak creative

Mar 2022 - July 2022

- Collaborating with a designer, I built a company website using Gatsby.js and deployed to AWS.
- Managing several companies' digital marketing. Handled Google ads, Google Analytics, Facebook, and Instagram ads. Seizing the clients' needs and reflecting that into a marketing strategy was a good experience and also helpful to my development skills.

Combat Engineer

Republic of Korea Marine Corps

Mar 2016 - Dec 2017

- Experienced hierarchical relationships, which taught me how to treat people, and took initiative to lead people.
- Participated in U.S. Korea joint training, harmonized the team to understand and accept other cultures as a squad leader which was a good experience to communicate with each other.

Skills

- Experienced end to end process of making products (ideation, design, development, and deployment)
- Collaboration with other developers using git-flow strategy.
- Have a strong understanding of user experience and reflect it into the development process.

Familiar Tech Stack:

- HTML5, CSS3(+frameworks), Typescript
- React / Gatsby / Next.js / State management (redux, thunk, saga)
- AWS / Vercel / Github / Git

Projects

#1 Collaboration tool suggestion App (Ongoing Team project)

- Suggest collaboration tools such as Notion, Slack, and Jira to the small teams who want to make a side project based on their personality.
- Working with 9 other team members including PM, UX/UI designers, and Backend developers.
- Tech used: React, Typescript, Storybook, and AWS.

#2 Caron automotive Website

- The Director of Caron automotive which is located in Tauranga requested me to build a website for the company.
- To their needs, I experienced the whole process from design to deployment.
- · Tech used: Figma, Gatsby, Sass, and AWS

#3 E-Commerce App (Team project)

- Working in a team to experience an agile development process to make an E-commerce CRUD Application. (MEVN stack)
- Proceed standup meetings and cooperate with team members from design to deploy process.
- Tech used: Vue, express, mongoDB, Node.js

#4 Hipeak Creative website

- Collaborate with a web designer, built a interactive, userfriendly company website.
- Tech used: Gatsby.js, AWS (cloudfront, S3, route53, rambda)

Education

Diploma in Web & UX design (Level 6) Yoobee college

July 2021 - July 2022

Diploma in Web Development & Design (Level 5) Toi Ohomai institute of technology 2020

Bachelor of Mechanical engineering Busan National University (South Korea)

Mar 2015 - Dec 2018

Interests

- I usually love working out and I am planning to participate in a body-building competition next year.
- Since my dad is a contemporary artist, I enjoy going to art galleries and exhibitions which inspires me with creative thinking.